This is Morioh Radio.
Kai Harada, here, keeping you
company on this fine day.
Now..
Just look at those spokes
sparkle and spin!
I can't believe I got
this mountain bike for graduation!
Getting new stuff is
so much fun!
I'm not gonna be able to give this up
for the school bus anytime soon!
O-Ow…
Wh-What the heck?
What's a bag doing
in the middle of the street?
No, it can't be!
That bag had a…
Oh-Oh my god!
I just ran it over!
I couldn't swerve in time!
It was right in my path!
I didn't even see it!
You got it.
It wasn't your fault.
Just an unfortunate accident.
The guy who shoved
a little kitten in a bag
and left it to die in the street
is the real scoundrel.
Pretty rotten if you ask me.
W-We've got to do something!
What's the point?
Do you hear any meowing?
It's dead.
What's your name?
I'm Tamami Kobayashi.
I graduated from your school
two years ago.
Nice bike ya got there.
You a freshman?
Y-Yes. My name's
Koichi Hirose.
Ah, that takes me back.
High school…
Those were the days.
Well, have a seat over here,
Mr. Hirose.
Eh? B-But…
Quit quivering…
I said sit your ass down!
Now…
I have a proposition for you.
I'll lay that pussycat to rest,
and you dish out a little cash.
Sound fair?
Hey! Something wrong
with your ears?!
Wh-What are you talking ab—
Hey, now.
This is serious business.
Of course, you're innocent,
but you're not planning on
just walking off
after killing my cat,
are you?
It was your cat?
That's what I said.
Y-You were the one who stuck
the kitten o-over there?
That's not the point.
I'm asking if you really think
you're gonna just walk away
scot free.
After all, the killer here…
is you, kiddo!
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
These faceless gazes pass by one another
A wound to the heart changes our everyday
Encounters without boundaries
The bizarre is our normal U-yeh
These ordinary mornings,
we're laughing on the surface
Mysteries drawn to each other,
identity still unknown
Without a heads up,
it's quietly lurking somewhere in this town
Although we bicker and complain
In the end, we celebrate
Dancing through the everyday
Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town
EPISODE 6
KOICHI HIROSE (REVERB)
So, feeling a little guilty, huh?
If paying a little fee
could free you from
that oppressive feeling of guilt…
Wouldn't it be easier
to just fork over some cash?
Right?
MONEY
Wh-What the heck is
this lock thing?!
It's so heavy!
Huh? You can see it?
Then this'll be a snap,
Hirose!
Th-This thing's a Stand?!
A Stand's stuck inside
my body?!
Hey, Josuke.
Look over there…
Isn't that Koichi?
Yep, that sure looks like
Koichi to me.
That guy always seems to
end up with the wrong crowd.
It doesn't look like
he's having a bad time.
Ya know,
I met this guy Keicho Nijimura
'bout four months ago,
and ended up with
a pretty handy skill.
Hadn't a clue what the hell
was happening,
but it sure made me happy.
I figured
if I put it to good use,
I'd be set for
the rest of my life.
Now…
Come on,
cough it up.
Be cheap, and
this lock is gonna stay put!
I-I don't…
have any money.
Huh… I thought
I just saw you look away.
W-Well…
This weight!
I can't bear the weight!
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
It's bad to lie, you know.
You lied and you know it,
am I right?
The guiltier you feel,
the bigger the lock grows.
This lock here is proportional
to the weight of your misdeed.
The two are inextricably linked.
Whether I'm sound asleep,
or you're running far away,
that thing isn't coming off.
Okay? So be a good boy,
and show me your wallet.
Come on.
Hey, you were
holding out on me.
This looks like
7,000 yen to me!
Th-That's my sneaker money
for gym class today!
Sneakers?
You can go barefoot!
What you up to, dude?
J-Josuke and Okuyasu!
Looks like a grown man's mugging
a little high school kid.
Go get a job and
earn your own money.
You know, little boys like
you should really stay out of this.
Sorry, no can do.
Not when there's a
stinkin' shit bag and
his dirty little Stand
in front of me.
I think it's time to
take out the trash.
Hey…
This thing won't come off.
Hey, wait…
You guys see it, too?
Just how many of you
are there?
That's what I'd like to know.
But the answer to that
can wait.
In the meantime, I'd appreciate
you removing that lock.
Hey, you goddamn punks!
Don't underestimate me!
I'm not fooling around!
Criminals must pay for their crimes.
That's how society works.
Or what? You gonna pay
me instead of Koichi?
If so, I'll let you guys go.
Money's money after all!
Oh? So you wanna try
and get money from me, huh?
Go ahead a try, prick!
Wait a second!
You just swiped 7,000 yen from me!
That's for lying to me, dolt!
Huh?!
You think that poor kitty's life
is only worth a measly 7,000 yen?
That's just not enough.
You owe me
five hundred grand for that.
Five hundred grand?!
Yes sirree, five hun—
Shut up, bitch!
O-Okuyasu!
Hey, control yourself.
I'm tired of your bullshit, bastard!
When I tell you to give his 7,000 yen
back, you give it back, douche bag!
Ouch! My front tooth!
Why the hell'd you stumble around
and make yourself fall over like that?
Make myself fall?
You're so mean!
How could you say that
after hitting me?!
My front tooth's
knocked out.
How could you be
so cruel?!
H-Hey, wait a sec…
Are you okay?
No, Okuyasu…
Don't let him make you feel guilty!
H-He did it on purpose!
A front tooth'll cost me a lot,
you know…
I don't have any insurance.
Wh-Why, you…
Uh oh! I wouldn't try anything
if I were you.
If anyone under my
lock's control tries to hurt me,
the damage will bounce
right back to the lock.
Y-You bastard…
Hey. That kitten you said
Koichi ran over…
Would it be this thing?
It was a stuffed animal?
Okay, let's see.
I've got your tooth right here.
There, good as new.
It's gone!
Hurrah!
I feel so much lighter now!
Wh-Who the hell are you?!
Hey, didja forget
about the 7,000 yen?
All right!
I'll give it back.
Put the money down,
and get the hell out of here,
dumb-ass!
Thank goodness… Ah!
Th-The bills…
H-He took the cash!
He grabbed enough of the bills
to exchange them at the bank!
Th-That bastard…
He's gonna pay!
And it's not even my money.
Damn.
A measly 7,000 yen.
Don't think
you've gotten away.
I remember.
Phew…
That rotten morning really
ruined my whole day.
I'm home, Police.
Hey, you alive?
Woof, woof.
I'm home.
I've heard all about you,
ma'am.
Beautiful, kind,
and so refined.
Oh, don't be silly.
I wouldn't lie!
Really?
Of course!
W- Why is this guy in my house
massaging my mom's shoulders?!
THE LOCK
TAMAMI KOBAYASHI
Y-You!
What are you doing here?!
Oh, Ko, you're home. Hi!
I-I s-said,
what are you doing here?!
This gentleman was
kind enough
to bring us the money
you dropped.
Huh?!
Seven thousand yen.
Mr. Forgetful.
Th-This money…
You told her you found it?
Of course!
You ran into Mr. Kobayashi
on your bike today, didn't you?
Wha…
I wanted to make sure
you got your money back, Koichi.
As you should!
Ko, why are you getting
so upset?
Ma'am,
this isn't easy for me to say,
but it seems
I too dropped my wallet
when Koichi hit me
with his bike.
And it looks just like this one.
Which means mine
was taken in place of his.
Do you understand what
I'm getting at, ma'am?
Well, it seems
almost inconceivable but…
I suppose it's possible.
So, please, ma'am, tell Koichi
to give me back my wallet.
It had about
five hundred thousand yen in there.
Please, tell him to give it back.
What?!
F-Five hundred thousand?!
So he finally said it!
I figured you out!
K-Ko…
Don't panic!
He's a fraud!
— Everything he says is lies!
— Oh, that's right.
I have proof
he swiped my wallet for his.
Last night, I had the
hamburger meal at Jonny's.
And… Oh, yeah. I added an
order of onion gratin soup…
The receipt was,
let's see, 1,833 yen…
It should be tucked away
somewhere in the wallet Koichi has.
K-Ko!
N-No! Mom,
you gotta believe me!
This is a trick!
You planted it on me!
Then you went out
and bought the same wallet!
You know,
that son of yours…
I hate to say it, habit or not,
that was really quite shameful.
This is the boy you raised…
As his mother,
you feel no guilt?
Stop!
M-Mom!
It finally appeared!
Now the weight of her guilt
will oppress her soul.
I'm gonna bleed you dry.
First, I'll take this house's
land, title, and seal.
What a great house
this place is.
Koichi,
is something wrong?
Sis!
Wh-What?!
When she brought me
some tea,
I got her to spill some
on my hand,
I wailed to make her think
she burned me.
She was so apologetic,
"I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry!"
She was so sweet
and seductive.
You said she's a junior at that
all-girls high school, right?
Fully grown and ripe
for the picking.
Y-Y-Yahoo!
How dare you?
I'll punish you!
I'll make you pay!
What the hell?
What is that
funny-looking egg thing?
What is that?!
Mom and Sis, I'll need
you to vacate the room!
Ko, what in the—?
I'll handle this.
I need you to be quiet!
Hey! G-Get that thing
away from me!
Your mom and sister
can leave the room,
but they're still
my hostages!
You're not getting anywhere
near my mother or sister!
Do it, Koichi!
If you're so strong, then do it!
Get those locks off
Mom and Sis now!
If your mom sees you beating
the shit outta me,
her guilt will grow
out of control!
I said, get those locks off!
You better respect
the great Tamami Kobayashi,
you little prick of
a pipsqueak!
L-Like hell
I'll remove the locks!
Huh? What?
That didn't hurt at all.
Huh?
Whoa! What was that?
That's a helluva sound,
but his little fists can't do squat!
What kind of Stand is that?
He doesn't have
a drop of speed or power!
How dare you startle me
like that, little halfwit?!
I'll show you!
A Stand's only
as powerful
as its wielder's
mental fortitude.
Which means your spirit is
feeble and weak!
— You're gonna pay dearly for this!
— Something's weird. His cheek!
A "ba"and "gi"?
It looks like
comic book sound effects.
Wh-What?
What's that weird ringing!
It's like the sound
I heard when he hit me…
What the hell is
this writing on my arm?!
I-It's stuck!
That can't be…
These sounds seem to be
coming from inside my body!
Your Stand did this?!
Damn you!
Stop this noise now!
It's sound.
My Stand permeates
the body with sound!
Wait a second,
I learned a famous Matsuo Basho
poem like this at school…
"Ah, the quietude—
Permeating the stones,
The locusts' trill."
Dammit!
He got me!
Remove the locks from my
mother and sister,
and the noise will stop!
If you don't,
who knows what might happen
to your body!
Stop these sounds!
Stop trying to be tough,
and remove the locks!
Goddamnit!
How dare you do this to me?!
You think I could swindle
and con you
if I were afraid of
a pissant like you!
The "Tama" in my name
stands for "balls"!
You'll find out
soon enough!
That knife doesn't scare me!
You've underestimated me!
You've never experienced
fear before!
Get ready for the
pain and panic of the padlock!
— Yeooow!
— What?!
Ow, ow, ow, ow,
ow, ow, ow, ow!
The cut is shallow,
and the scream is fake!
Toss!
"Toss"?
Who's screaming?
What's wrong?
Ko?!
This isn't…
S-Shit!
Yes!
K-Ko!
How could you do this?!
No, Mom!
You've got it all wrong!
No!
Sis!
I win! You lose!
Now, hurry up and
get rid of this racket, Koichi!
If you don't,
your mom will be
crushed by guilt!
And when a person becomes
overwhelmed with guilt,
death sounds
a lot better than life.
T-That's it…
I can't stand it anymore!
Mom!
I can't live
like this anymore!
Stop trying to be
so tough!
Stop the sound now!
You want your mom to kill herself?!
No, I won't do you the favor.
In fact, I'll make it worse!
Believe me!
What?!
You gotta believe me,
Mom!
Believe me!
It all depends on a person's soul!
She'll never believe you!
Mom…
Of course… If I, his own mother,
can't believe him,
who will?
Koichi's always been
an angel.
He'd never hurt a soul.
He'd never steal!
Yes!
Oh no!
Mom!
Blast it!
Parents never trust
their kids…
Mine never did!
Gulp…
It was a joke!
Ko, it was all a joke!
Take the lock off
my sister, too.
I already took it off!
I could never do anything
to harm that beautiful face!
I was only kidding
about taking your house!
I even gave back
your 7,000 yen.
'Member? 'member?
Please forgive me!
I'll do anything, Master Koichi!
Really?
You'll do anything?
Yes, Master Koichi!
I'll do anything!
I'll be your underling!
All right, then…
Make sure you bring me five
hundred grand by tomorrow.
That's a joke.
Only a joke.
I-It sure didn't sound like it!
H-Hey, Okuyasu! What the hell
is this guy doing?
Please give me the honor
of carrying your bag to school!
You really want to carry it?
Of course I do!
Master Koichi!
You're a man among men!
Come on,
cut that out.
Hey, Okuyasu!
Don't ask me!
I'm not the smart one,
remember?
EPISODE 7
TOSHIKAZU HAZAMADA (SHOW OFF)